Adam Mosebach

Full Stack Web Developer New York. NY

Professional Summary

I am a developer with a passion for thinking outside the box. I believe there are many solutions to achieving a goal and love finding the best one. I am a fun-loving but focused person who finds fulfillment in completing a task. Efficiency and user experience fuel my logical approach to crafting the ideal product.

Related Experience

Software Engineering Immersive Fellow

General Assembly | New York | 2020-Present

- Built and deployed projects with a React front-end and a MongoDB or Rails backend
- Worked on solo projects as well as in teams, dominated by a creative and collaborative atmosphere
- Daily morning stand-ups with either your team or supervising lead
- · Peer review provided alternative solutions to problems

Morgan Stanley

Programmer | New York | 2006-2007

- Wrote automated processes for incoming trade records to be ingested and analyzed
- Provided error reporting for both the client and Morgan Stanley
- Provided customer service to large firms when further action was needed on client side
- Built a series of training videos to help incoming colleagues perform and onboard efficiently

Other Work

AJ Karaoke

Founder, Owner, Operator | 2014-Present

- Combined many machines to create a full setup for audio and visual technology
- Used Virtual DJ program to implement songs and project lyrics to screen
- Consistently updated the online catalog using a database and elementary php

Professional Actor

Various Locations | 2007-2019

 Actor (and sometimes assistant stage manager) in various theaters across America, including a national tour and an international tour

Contact

Phone: 516.721.2784

Email: adam.mosebach.dev@gmail.com

LinkedIn/in/adammosebach

Technical Skills

JAVASCRIPT REACT
HTML GIT
CSS RUBY

EXPRESS RUBY ON RAILS
NODE.JS POSTGRESQL
MONGO DB COMMAND LINE

MONGOOSE RESTful APIs

JSON/AJAX RESPONSIVE DESIGN

Education

Certificate of Completion

General Assembly

New York, NY

Bachelor of Fine Arts

- minor in Computer Applications

NYU

New York, NY

Portfolio

AdamMosebach.dev